http://uucsjs.org/website-privacy-policy/

Skip to Main Content
Search for:
Search
Google Map
Unitarian Universalist Congregation of the South Jersey Shore
Mailing address:
PO Box 853
Pomona, NJ 08240
GPS:
39°30'03.0"N   74°31'58.5"W
Physical address:
(DO NOT USE FOR MAILING!)
75 South Pomona Road
Egg Harbor City, NJ 08215
Office Phone: (609) 965-9400
Email:
Administrator: uucsjsadmin@gmail.com
Minister: minister@uucsjs.org
Unitarian Universalist Congregation of the South Jersey Shore
Contact Us
PO Box 853, Pomona NJ 08240 | 609.965.9400 | uucsjsadmin@gmail.com
Sunday Services: 10:00 am
Website Privacy Policy
This website is owned and operated by UUCSJS, referred to in this policy as “we”. We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This privacy policy addresses those concerns. This policy may be changed or updated from time to time.
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: uucsjsadmin@gmail.com.
We are available to answer your questions or hear your concerns.
The first principle of Unitarian Universalism is to covenant to affirm and promote the inherent worth and dignity of every person. We believe that this principle impels us to protect the privacy of visitors.
Personal Information
Our site does not collect personal information from our visitors.
Statistical Information Collected
We collect information on the browsing habits of users and the companies that provide that service also have access to that information. This site collects information using cookies and javascript, so if they are enabled in your browser, information can be collected, such as your browser type, operating system, IP address, and country. This information is only used for statistical purposes and cannot identify you as an individual.
Information Accuracy
We make every effort to ensure that the information presented is correct and accurate. If inaccuracies occur, we will make every effort to correct them in a timely manner. To report any web site inaccuracies or for questions about our Privacy Policy please email us at webtech@uucsjs.com.
Links to Third Party Sites
Our web sites contain some hyperlinks to web sites operated by parties other than UUCSJS. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference only. We do not control such web sites and are not responsible for their contents or privacy policies. The inclusion of hyperlinks to other web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on these Web sites or any association with their operators.
Section Navigation
Member Information
Latest news…
Sunday, January 3, 2021 | My Dream for Our Congregation | UUCSJS Board Members
Sunday, December 27, 2020 | NO SERVICE TODAY
Sunday, December 20, 2020 | The Stillness of Midwinter | Rev. Dawn Fortune
Sunday, December 13, 2020 | In the Quiet, We Wait | Rev. Dawn Fortune
Sunday, December 6, 2020 | Stillness as a double-edged thing | Rev. Dawn Fortune
Wednesday, November 4, 2020, 6pm | Post-Election Vigil
Sunday, November 29, 2020 | Forgive Me | Lay speaker Paul Utts
Sunday, November 22, 2020 | Book Lovers Group
Sunday, November 15, 2020 | Breathe In, Breathe Out | Rev. Dawn Fortune
Sunday, November 8, 2020 | Now What? | Rev. Dawn Fortune
